Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers YCAL MSS 722
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2008 Acquisition, circa 1916-2008; 344633; 100.63 Linear Feet (117 boxes) + 2 broadside folders, 8 rolls, 2 record albums
  - Personal and Other Papers, circa 1925-2003; 344697
    - Family Papers, 344760
      - Certificates, Arthur Kramer / 1916 Class Reunion photograph, George Kramer, circa 1950s-1960s; 344791
      - Certificates, Rea Kramer, circa 1920s-1930s; 344790
      - Clippings, 344789 (Box 138)
      - "Death of George L. Kramer", circa 1968; 344788; 3 Folders (Box 138)
      - Diary, circa 1933; 344787 (Box 138)
      - Diary, "My Trip to the West Coast", circa 1947; 344786 (Box 138)
      - Diary, "Incl. 'Death in Positano...' ", circa 1970; 344785 (Box 138)
      - "Diplomas, school and Address book", 344784 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Arthur - letterman jacket patch, circa 1944; 344783 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Arthur - Navy Orders, circa 1944; 344782 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, George and Rea - "Grand Circle Tour", circa 1964; 344781 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Larry - "Letters to mother", circa 1964-1967; 344780 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea, 344779 (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea - letters, circa 1925-1941; 344778; 2 Folders (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea - Travel documents, 344777; 2 Folders (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Rea and George - Letters, 344776 (Box 139)
      - "Material related to travels", circa 1960s; 344775 (Box 139)
      - The Onondagan, circa 1925; 344774 (Box 139)
      - Papers, loose, 344773 (Box 139)
      - Photograph Album, 344772; 2 Folders (Box 139)
      - Photograph Album - "My Grandchildren", 344771 (Box 139)
      - Photographic portraits, 344770
      - Photographs, 344769; 5 Folders (Box 139)
      - Photographs of Larry and Arthur Kramer, 344768 (Box 139)
      - Postcards, 344767 (Box 139)
      - Printed family material, 344766 (Box 139)
      - "The Sam Hanky Color Code handkerchief ", 344765 (Box 139)
      - Scrapbook, 344764
      - Tefillin, 344763; 2 Folders (Box 139)
        Includes the two parts of a tefillin, also known as phylacteries.
      - Yale Class of 1916 - Reunion in Print, circa 1942; 344762 (Box 139)
      - Yale Moot Court of Appeals, circa 1951; 344761 (Box 139)
    - Household Papers, 344755
      - Connecticut expenses, 344759 (Box 140)
      - Connecticut house, 344758 (Box 140)
      - Connecticut mortgage, 344757; 2 Folders (Box 140)
      - Various, 344756; 2 Folders (Box 140)
    - Medical Records, 344744
      - A.A.R.P., circa 1994; 344754 (Box 140)
      - AETNA Insurance, circa 1990; 344753 (Box 140)
      - Blue Choice HMO, circa 1996; 344752; 2 Folders (Box 140)
      - Blue Cross, circa 1993-1994; 344751; 6 Folders (Box 140)
        Includes radiographs (x-rays).
      - Blue Cross, circa 1993-1995; 344750; 5 Folders (Box 141)
      - Caremark, circa 1996; 344749 (Box 141)
      - Community Prescription, circa 1995; 344748 (Box 141)
      - Health Records, circa 2002-2003; 344747; 4 Folders (Box 141)
      - Writers Guild Insurance, circa 1989; 344746 (Box 141)
      - X-rays, 344745
    - Other Papers, 344737
      - Awards, 344743
      - Honorary award, The Normal Heart theater event benefiting the Gay Men's Health Crisis, 344742
      - Personal mentions, circa 1990s; 344741; 10 Folders (Box 141)
      - Personal mentions, circa 1990s; 344740; 7 Folders (Box 142)
      - Royalty Earnings, circa 1990s; 344739 (Box 142)
      - T-Shirts and Hats, 344738 (Box 143)
    - Printed Material, 344718
      - AIDS activism, posters, 344736
      - Various speaking events, posters, 344735
      - The Destiny of Me, posters, 344734
      - Faggots, posters, 344733
      - Four Friends, posters, 344732
      - The Normal Heart, posters, 344731
      - Women in Love, posters, 344730
      - The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me, poster, circa 2000; 344729
      - The Tragedy of Today's Gays, poster, circa 2005; 344728
      - Rolled posters, unsorted, 344727
        Includes posters for movies, plays, and speaking events, as well as ones dealing with AIDS activism.
      - Miscellaneous printed, 344726
      - Book, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans who make a Difference, by Barbaralee Diomonstein, circa 1997; 344725 (Box 144)
      - Magazines, circa 1949-1990s; 344724; 4 Folders (Box 144)
      - Magazines, circa 1980s-2000s; 344723; 12 Folders (Box 145)
      - Magazines, circa 1990-2008; 344722; 13 Folders (Box 146)
      - Newspapers, circa 1970s-2000s; 344721; 5 Folders (Box 147)
      - "Printed Mentions", circa 1989-1993; 344720; 6 Folders (Box 147)
      - "Printed Mentions", 344719; 4 Folders (Box 148)
    - Photographs, 344700
      - Arnold, Eve, circa 1965; 344717 (Box 148)
      - "Book Party", 344716 (Box 148)
      - Davis, Brad - head shot, 344715 (Box 148)
      - "Europe", 344714 (Box 148)
      - Family photographs, circa 1900s -1980s; 344713; 6 Folders (Box 148)
      - Gunderson, Gary - Larry Kramer portrait, circa 1995; 344712 (Box 148)
      - Hill, Ethan, circa 2001; 344711 (Box 148)
      - Hill, Ethan, circa 2001; 344710; 2 Folders (Box 149)
      - Kramer, Larry, 344709; 5 Folders (Box 149)
      - Kramer, Larry, by Annie Leibovitz, 344708
      - Mulberry Bush, 344707 (Box 149)
      - Personal photographs, including negatives, circa 1952-1980s; 344706; 9 Folders (Box 149)
      - Snapshots and portraits of Larry Kramer, including slides, 344705 (Box 149)
      - Snapshots and portraits of Larry Kramer, including slides, 344704; 4 Folders (Box 150)
      - Various photographs, including negatives, circa 1966; 344703; 2 Folders (Box 150)
      - Various slides and negatives, 344702; 2 Folders (Box 150)
      - Women in Love, circa 1969; 344701; 7 Folders (Box 150)
    - Framed print of the poem "Bore," inscribed "Love, Charlie", 344699
    - Wall mural by Larry Kramer, 344698
  - Audiovisual Material, circa 1967-1990s; 344688
    Box 233 contains a stand-alone list of what appears to be recorded television segments on Kramer and AIDS-related content. It is not married to a particular video cassette.
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&63830b00-6082-46d5-a0a1-0c825af20b42
    - Audiocassettes, circa 1980s-1990s; 344696 (Box 151)
      Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      Includes audio recordings of interviews, meetings, events, and a Simon & Schuster "The Normal Heart" production, as well as unlabelled cassettes with unknown material. Also includes a John Bucchino cassette (circa 1991) called "Solitude Lessons."
      - Untitled, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:02:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889135)
      - "Larry King Show", 1989 April 6; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889143)
      - "Sleep Easy", Summit Counseling Ctr., undated; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889150)
      - "Ride the Chariot", Yale Glee Club, 1987; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889168)
      - Fuch writ re Mayor / Judy Peabody, 1988 January 2; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889176)
      - "Meridian: AIDS in the Arts", 1991 January 22; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889184)
      - John Bucchino, Solitude Lessons, 1991; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151)
        This is a commercial audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
      - Untitled, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:24:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889192)
      - Larry Kramer, BJS, CIS, "Normal Heart", 1994 January 31, February 2-3; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:47:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889200)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:57:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889218)
      - "The Normal Heart", Act 1, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:07:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889226)
      - "The Normal Heart", Act 2, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:06:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889234)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 1, 1986 April; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889242)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 2, 1986 April; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889259)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 3, 1986 April; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889267)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 4, 1987 July; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889275)
      - Radio Free America #16, AIDS: Epidemic or Weapon of War?, Dave Emory, tape 5, 1987 July; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889283)
      - Project inform, "Update Town Meeting, Notes from Amsterdam" (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1992 August 26; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889291)
      - Project inform, "Update Town Meeting, Notes from Amsterdam" (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1992 August; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889309)
      - "Remembering Stonewall", undated; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889317)
      - "Defamation", narrated by Harvey Fierstein, undated; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889325)
      - Project inform, "AIDS Treatment Update", 1993 October 29; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889333)
      - Project inform,"Town Meeting", September 29; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889341)
      - "May Update", undated; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889358)
      - "April Town Meeting", undated; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889366)
      - Project inform, "August Town Meeting", undated; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889374)
      - "Berlin Update", undated; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889382)
      - Larry, Astrology, tape #1 (1 of 3 audiocassettes), 1992 September; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:02:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889390)
      - Larry, Astrology, tape #2 (2 of 3 audiocassettes), 1992 September; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:02:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889408)
      - Larry, Astrology, tape #3 (3 of 3 audiocassettes), 1992 September; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:51:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program starts and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889416)
      - "Ideas", AIDS (#7), CBC Radio, 1989 April; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889424)
      - "Ideas", AIDS (#8), CBC Radio, 1989 May; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 151, Item barcode 39002104889432)
    - Phonograph records, 45 rpm, 344693
      - "Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush," by Traffic, three copies, circa 1967; 344695 (Box 184 (Record Album Storage))
      - Cyril Stapleton and His Orchestra performing "Women in Love," four copies, circa 1970; 344694 (Box 185 (Record Album Storage))
    - Audiotape reels, circa 1960s; 344692
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&027acd70-619e-455b-9587-34efb0fda5c1
      - "Women in Love", tape 1, copy 2, #1 to #6, undated; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:30:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program was recorded at a very high level. The program was distorted at times. Mulitple gaps of 20 seconds or more are present on the reel. High amounts of hum are present. (Box 186, Item barcode 39002104889119)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3d031c25-2837-459a-96ae-a568af35999a
      - "Women in Love", tape 2, copy 2, #7 to #14, undated; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:27:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 186, Item barcode 39002104889127)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&899bf34a-51e5-4cd3-9810-9a404d027568
    - Videocassettes, circa 1980s-1990s; 344691
      Includes video recordings of "The Normal Heart", a four-part documentary "A Time of AIDS," Charlie Rose interviews (circa 1990s), and various other interviews and events.
      - Gay Pride '93, Jonathan Hardary intro to Larry Kramer (49 sec.), 1993; YCALMSS722_0001; 655224; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:30:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337509)
      - Living Proof: HIV and the Pursuit of Happiness, seventh rough cut, no sound work, 1993 May 24; YCALMSS722_0002; 655225; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:10:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A timecode run through the entire tape. (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337517)
      - Out in America, Lovett Productions, Inc., WNET-Thirteen, one hour, 1991 June 26; YCALMSS722_0003; 655226; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:59:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337525)
      - A Time of AIDS: I. The Zero Factor, undated; YCALMSS722_0004; 655227; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:02:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337533)
      - A Time of AIDS: II. Hunting the Virus, undated; YCALMSS722_0005; 655229; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:02:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337541)
      - A Time of AIDS: III. Fighting for Life, undated; YCALMSS722_0006; 655231; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:01:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337558)
      - A Time of AIDS: IV. The End of the Beginning, undated; YCALMSS722_0007; 655232; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:16:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337566)
      - Charlie Rose interview with Larry Kramer, 1993 April 5; YCALMSS722_0008; 655235; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:57:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337574)
      - Charlie Rose interview with Larry Kramer, 1993 August 10; YCALMSS224_0002; 655236; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:02:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337582)
      - Charlie Rose interview with Larry Kramer, 1995 January 18; YCALMSS722_0010; 655238; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:18:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337590)
      - Larry Kramer speech at the AIDS Institute Conference, Albany, 1993 November 14; YCALMSS722_0011; 655239; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:36:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337608)
      - Larry Kramer, Albany Healthcare Workers, 1993 November; YCALMSS722_0012; 655240; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:59:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337616)
      - BBC The Late Show, Out in America, undated; YCALMSS722_0013; 655242; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:43:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); NTSC (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337624)
      - Testing the Limits, 28 minutes, undated; YCALMSS722_0014; 655251; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:32:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337632)
      - AIDS Quarterly, 1989 Winter; YCALMSS722_0015; 655258; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:45:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337640)
      - Hoffman-Laroche Community Advisory Board Action: Marriot Marquis, New York City, 1993 January 16; YCALMSS722_0016; 655260; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337657)
      - Newsmaker Sunday, 1993 April 25; YCALMSS722_0017; 655261; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:28:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337665)
      - Arena: Larry Kramer (Kramer v Kramer) 60 minutes, undated; YCALMSS722_0018; 655263; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:55:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337673)
      - Nightline, ABC News, 1991 November 7; YCALMSS722_0019; 655264; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:47:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337681)
      - Target Bush (AIDS Community Television), 1993; YCALMSS722_0020; 655603; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:29:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416899)
      - The Normal Heart, Hollywood Playhouse, 1989 December 14; YCALMSS722_0021; 655604; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 02:39:27 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416907)
      - The Normal Heart, reading Cape Cod, recorded by Tim McCarthy, undated; YCALMSS722_0022; 655605; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 02:39:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416915)
      - The Normal Heart, Southern Utah University, Ana Dittmar, 1991 May 6; YCALMSS722_0023; 655606; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:05:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416923)
      - The Normal Heart, P.M. (PM Magazine), undated; YCALMSS722_0024; 655607; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:56:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416931)
        "Normal Heart" segment runs 00:04:45 in length. The rest of the tape is media coverage of the U.S. strike against Libya.
      - Larry Kramer Interview and ATAC Opening Speech, recorded by Tim McCarthy, 1990 November 10; YCALMSS722_0025; 655608; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:46:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The audio is a little bit low. (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416949)
      - Larry Kramer, BBCtv, part one, 1993 August 19; YCALMSS722_0026; 655609; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 02:22:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416956)
      - Larry Kramer, BBCtv, part two, 1993 August 20; YCALMSS722_0027; 655610; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:33:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416964)
      - Larry Kramer/Kathleen Sullivan CBS Morning Show, 1989 November 30; YCALMSS722_0028; 655612; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 02:04:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416972)
      - Gay Pride Weekend, Statue of Liberty, Fireworks, Shelter Island Garden, 1990; YCALMSS722_0029; 655613; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 03:58:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416980)
      - Roger McFarlane/Larry Kramer GMHC 81-99, Hunter College Graduate School of Public Health, 1988 November; YCALMSS722_0030; 655614; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:43:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102416998)
      - 0054-2054 Sources 1995 March 2 "Gay Men and AIDS" Larry Kramer, Gabriel Rotello, Dennis DeLeon; 2054-3466 CLGR Forum on sex clubs, Levin Osborne, Rotello 1995 February 16, 1995 March 2; 1995 February 16; YCALMSS722_0031; 655615; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 02:03:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337921)
      - Larry Kramer on "The Phil Donahue Show", 2/13/90, 1990 February; YCALMSS722_0032; 655619; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:57:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337939)
        This tape has Larry Kramer as a guest on the Phil Donahue Show.
      - Lucille Lortel Awards, 1993 May 17; YCALMSS722_0033; 655620; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:42:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337947)
      - Basic Instinct/SF Queer Nation protests, undated; YCALMSS722_0034; 655622; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:31:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 152, Item barcode 39002102337954)
      - Day One, 1993 March 28; YCALMSS722_0036; 655623; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:26:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337962)
        Restricted fragile material.
      - "Rights and Reactions" by Phil Zwickler and Jane Lippman, undated; YCALMSS722_0036; 655624; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:55:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The in the first segment of the video is very low. The video is in poor condition. (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337970)
        A note from Phil Zwickler to Larry Kramer reads: Dear Larry- You are a jewel - a specimen of [earth] cherished for its beauty and power to inspire - Love Phil
      - Roger [McFarland] on Morton Downey Jr. Show, 1987; YCALMSS722_0037; 655625; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 01:01:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337988)
        This is an episode of "The Morton Downey Jr. Show". It includes a segment on whether people with AIDS should be quarantined.
      - Broadway Bares IV, Broadway Beat, undated; YCALMSS722_0038; 655626; 1 Videocassettes (VHS); 00:49:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102337996)
      - Donahue, #11172 - AIDS, YCALMSS722_0039; 655628; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic); 00:58:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 233, Item barcode 39002102338002)
  - Oversize Material, circa 1916-1998; 344654
    - Just Say No (from Writing Files), circa 1988; 344687 (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - The Normal Heart (from Writing Files), circa 1989; 344686 (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - The Normal Heart (from Writing Files), circa 1985-1989; 344685; 3 Folders (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - AIDS General, Philadelphia, the movie (from Professional Papers and Research Material), 344684 (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - AIDS Activism, ACT UP (from Professional Papers and Research Material), 344683 (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - Research Material (from Professional Papers and Research Material), circa 1980s-1998; 344682 (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - Interviews of and Articles by Larry Kramer (from Professional Papers and Research Material), 344681 (Box 157 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Album (from Personal and Other Papers), 344680 (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Art Prints (from Personal and Other Papers), 344679 (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Photographic portraits (from Personal and Other Papers), 344678 (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Scrapbook (from Personal and Other Papers), 344677 (Box 158 (Oversize))
    - Medical Records, X-rays (from Personal and Other Papers), 344676 (Box 159 (Oversize))
    - Other Papers, Awards (from Personal and Other Papers), 344675 (Box 159 (Oversize))
    - Other Papers, Honorary award, The Normal Heart theater event benefiting the Gay Men's Health Crisis (from Personal and Other Papers), 344674 (Box 159 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, AIDS activism, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1980s; 344673 (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Various speaking events, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), 344672 (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, The Destiny of Me, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), 344671 (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Faggots, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), 344670 (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Four Friends, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), 344669 (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, The Normal Heart, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), 344668 (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Women in Love, posters (from Personal and Other Papers), 344667 (Box 160 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Miscellaneous printed (from Personal and Other Papers), 344666 (Box 161 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Magazines (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1958-1981; 344665 (Box 161 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1980s-1990s; 344664; 2 Folders (Box 161 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1983-1985; 344663; 3 Folders (Box 162 (Oversize))